CURRICULUM VITAE

Mr Matthew Bryce Turner (23)

30 Auction Close, Ashbourne, United Kingdom DE61GQ

Mobile Number: 079 8119 8192 E-mail: mattyturn95@gmail.com

Date of birth: 15/06/1995

Nationality: British/South African

Profile

I have recently immigrated to the UK, to sustain a better career path. I am especially interested in pursuing a web development orientated career, whereby I can show my full potential in a competitive environment. Prior to relocating, I have had two years internal sales experience, working for Burquip International (Pty) Ltd; a large truck and trailer manufacturing company in South Africa. This job enabled me to develop key skills paramount to my success. Which is evident in my promotion, after two months, to an internal sales executive. In addition, I was successful in meeting and often exceeding goals and targets set by management.

I am also well into my Computer Science studies and have almost completed my level 5 diploma through the Code Institute.

Core Accomplishments

- Swellendam 1st XV Rugby 2014
- Boland U18 Lsen Rugby 2015
- South African U18 LSEN Rugby Academy 2015
- FireMaster Certificate (2017)

Key Skills

- Good Time management (work deadlines)
- Good work ethic (progression in ranks)
- Organised
- Driven
- Ambitious
- Presentable
- Resilient
- · Team player

Engaging with customers.

I enjoy personal contact with existing customers as well as building relationships with new clients.

Promoting new products

Part of my job description at Burquip International was to promote new products to new and existing clients.

Achieving and reporting on sales targets

I am comfortable with the pressure of meeting sales targets.

Professional experience

• The Bowling Green, , Ashbourne DE6 1GG

(2nd September 2018 – present) Waiter/bartender

Basic Bistro, Stellenbosch, South Africa

(July 2017- January 2018) Waiter/Bartender

Burquip International (Pty) Ltd, Cape Town, South Africa

(3rd March 2016 – 25th July 2017) Sales executive. Reason for leaving: relocation.

Education

 I am currently studying towards a Level 5 Diploma in Computer Science (Full Stack web Developer)

Studied a BBA (Bachelors of Business & Administration) Through IMM.

Was not able to Complete due to relocating to the UK.

Subjects Passed

Financial Management 101 Academic Literacy Business Management 101 Marketing 101 Statistics 101

> National Senior Certificate, Glenwood Boys High school January 2009 – December 2015
> (Equivalent to GCSE's and A-Level's in the UK)

Subjects Passed

English Home Language

Afrikaans 1st additional language

Mathematical Literacy

Life Orientation

Business Studies

History

Tourism

References

Burquip International (PTY) Ltd. (Please Find attached Reference Letter below)

Name: Mr Jacques Viviers

Address: Saxenwold Lane, Blackheath Cape Town

Email: Jacques@burquip.co.za

Glenwood Boys High School

Name: Mrs A Barnes

Address: 1ZK Matthew road, Durban, South Africa

Email: Abarnes@glenwoodhighschool.co.za

The Bowling Green

Name: David Paterson

Email: d@pat.com

It is my great pleasure to write this letter of recommendation for Matthew Turner.

Based on my interaction with Matthew during his time of employment at Burquip International (3 March 2016 to 25 July 2017), as a store assistant (2 months) and sales executive, I can state with confidence that he is a self-disciplined, self-motivated and a responsible person. He consistently demonstrated all of these qualities and more, and I heartily endorse him for any customer service position.

His work was consistently completed on time, and he participated actively with valuable contributions. Matthew multitasks effectively and is able to handle a high-volume workload.

He consistently met or surpassed all weekly call centre metrics and sales to walk-in clients (including customer satisfaction, call volume and response time), and his daily written reports' were accurate and thorough.

I strongly believe he has tremendous potential and wish him the very best for all his future endeavours.

Regards

Jacques Viviers

Branch Manager



Burquip International (Pty) Ltd PO Box 281, Kuils River 7579 Saxenburg Rd, Blackheath 7581 Tel. +27 (0) 21 907-1900

Fax. +27 (0) 21 907-1999 Email: <u>jacques@burquip.co.za</u> Web: <u>www.burquip.co.za</u>

"http://www.burquip.co .za/"

Directors: J.L. Burke, A.A. de Villiers, K.C.O. Bergh, H. Millward, F.J. Carstens Registration Number 1991/004127/07